ILGWU. Carl Proper papers 5780/150
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
- Fashion Institute of Technology (FIT): Export Program, 1993 (Box 35, Folder 17)
- Fashion Institute of Technology (FIT): Small Business Center, 1993 (Box 35, Folder 18)
- Focus Groups, 1990 (Box 35, Folder 19)
- General Advisory Council (GAC), 1993 (Box 35, Folder 20)
- General Advisory Council (GAC): Meeting, 1990 (Box 35, Folder 21)
  November 12-14
- General Advisory Council (GAC): Survey, 1993 (Box 35, Folder 22)
- General Advisory Council (GAC): Labor-Management Advisory Committee, 1992-1994 (Box 35, Folder 23)
- General Advisory Council (GAC): Labor-Management Advisory Committee Folder, 1994 (Box 35, Folder 24)
- General Advisory Council (GAC): Labor-Management Advisory Committee Initial Membership (Box 35, Folder 25)
- General Advisory Council (GAC): Talk Notes, 1994 (Box 35, Folder 26)
  December
- General Advisory Council (GAC): Background, 1994 (Box 35, Folder 27)
- General Executive Board (GEB), 1994 (Box 35, Folder 28)
- General Executive Board (GEB): Meeting, 1994 (Box 35, Folder 29)
- General Executive Board (GEB): Meeting, 1994 (Box 35, Folder 30)
- General Executive Board (GEB): First UNITE Meeting, 1995 (Box 35, Folder 31)
- Garment Industry Development Corporation (GIDC), 1992 (Box 35, Folder 32)
- Garment Industry Development Corporation (GIDC), 1993 (Box 35, Folder 33)
- Garment Industry Development Corporation (GIDC): Activity Reports, 1992-1994 (Box 35, Folder 34)
- Garment Industry Development Corporation (GIDC): Projects with ACTWU, 1995 (Box 35, Folder 35)
- Garment Industry Development Corporation (GIDC): Board Member List, 1994 (Box 35, Folder 36)
- Garment Industry Development Corporation (GIDC): Budget Dispute Internal Memos, 1995 (Box 35, Folder 37)
- Garment Industry Development Corporation (GIDC): Budget Core Issues, 1995 (Box 35, Folder 38)
- Garment Industry Development Corporation (GIDC): Budget New York State Issues, 1995 (Box 35, Folder 39)
- Garment Industry Development Corporation (GIDC): Funding Sources, 1992-1994 (Box 35, Folder 40)
- Garment Industry Development Corporation (GIDC): Funding Grants, 1991-1992 (Box 35, Folder 41)
- Garment Industry Development Corporation (GIDC): Focus Groups on Quick Response, 1991-1993 (Box 35, Folder 42)
- Garment Industry Development Corporation (GIDC): Chinatown Contractor Quality Control, 1993 (Box 35, Folder 43)
  English and Chinese September
- Garment Industry Development Corporation (GIDC): Management Survey, 1992 (Box 35, Folder 44)
- Garment Industry Development Corporation (GIDC): Modernization Forum Proposal, 1994 (Box 35, Folder 45)
- Garment Industry Development Corporation (GIDC): Budget, 1994-1995 (Box 35, Folder 46)
- Garment Industry Development Corporation (GIDC): Budget, 1992-1993 (Box 35, Folder 47)
- Garment Industry Development Corporation (GIDC): Services and Work Referrals, 1989-1991 (Box 35, Folder 48)
- Garment Industry Development Corporation (GIDC): Lloyd Quality Project, 1994 (Box 35, Folder 49)
- Garment Industry Development Corporation (GIDC): Quarterly Reports, 1995 (Box 35, Folder 50)
- Incubator: Fashion Institute of Technology (FIT), 1994-1995 (Box 36, Folder 1)
- Incubator: Toronto, 1991-1995 (Box 36, Folder 2)
- Garment Industry Development Corporation (GIDC): Quarterly Reports, 1994 (Box 36, Folder 3)
- Garment Industry Development Corporation (GIDC): Quick Response Project, 1992-1994 (Box 36, Folder 4)
- Garment Industry Development Corporation (GIDC): Record of Services, 1988 (Box 36, Folder 5)
- Garment Industry Development Corporation (GIDC): Strategic Industries Group Services (SIGS) Proposal, 1994 (Box 36, Folder 6)
- Garment Industry Development Corporation (GIDC): Bios (Box 36, Folder 7)
- Garment Industry Development Corporation (GIDC): Staff Summaries, 1994 (Box 36, Folder 8)
- Garment Industry Development Corporation (GIDC): Summaries, 1994-1995 (Box 36, Folder 9)
- Garment Industry Development Corporation (GIDC): Council for American Fashion (CAF) Summaries, 1993-1994 (Box 36, Folder 10)
- Garment Industry Development Corporation (GIDC): Training Programs, 1993 (Box 36, Folder 11)
- Garment Industry Development Corporation (GIDC): Training and Extension Programs, 1995 (Box 36, Folder 12)
- Garment Industry Development Corporation (GIDC): Vendor Report, 1995 (Box 36, Folder 13)
- Complete Paper Set of Transparencies (Box 36, Folder 14)
- Graphics: Doc Briefing, 1994 (Box 36, Folder 15)
  January 28
- Graphics: General Information and Presentations (Box 36, Folder 16)
- Graphics: Old Less Used (Box 36, Folder 17)
- Graphics: Washington (Box 36, Folder 18)
- Graphics: Union Organizing (Box 36, Folder 19)
- Health and Safety: Factory Fires (Box 36, Folder 20)
- ILGWU Convention, 1995 (Box 36, Folder 21)
- ILGWU Economics, 1984 (Box 36, Folder 22)
- Labor-Management Summaries, 1991 (Box 36, Folder 23)
- Textile Research Institute, 1994-1995 (Box 36, Folder 24)
- Brian Uzzi, 1991-1995 (Box 36, Folder 25)
- Staff Training, 1992 (Box 36, Folder 26)
- Local 10 Cutting Class, 1992-1993 (Box 36, Folder 27)
- Staff Training: Pennsylvania, 1990 (Box 36, Folder 28)
- Staff Meetings: Pennsylvania, 1990 (Box 36, Folder 29)
- Staff Training: New England, 1990 (Box 36, Folder 30)
- Strategic Analysis Working Group, 1992-1993 (Box 36, Folder 31)
- Third World, 1989-1991 (Box 36, Folder 32)
- Trade: Social Clause, 1994 (Box 36, Folder 33)
- Trade: Global Sourcing, 1994 (Box 36, Folder 34)
- National Institute of Standards and Technology (NIST): Networks, 1992 (Box 36, Folder 35)
- Federal-State Industrial Modernization, 1992 (Box 36, Folder 36)
  July
- National Institute of Standards and Technology (NIST): State Technology Extension Program (STEP), 1993 (Box 36, Folder 37)
- Demand Activated Manufacturing Architecture (DAMA): Meeting Amtex, 1994-1995 (Box 37, Folder 1)
- Demand Activated Manufacturing Architecture (DAMA), 1996 (Box 37, Folder 2)
- Amtex, 1996 (Box 37, Folder 3)
- Demand Activated Manufacturing Architecture (DAMA): Plans, 1995 (Box 37, Folder 4)
- Amtex Directory, 1994 (Box 37, Folder 5)
- Amtex / Demand Activated Manufacturing Architecture (DAMA): General Information, 1994-1995 (Box 37, Folder 6)
- Amtex / Demand Activated Manufacturing Architecture (DAMA): Reports, 1993-1994 (Box 37, Folder 7)
- Boston, 1997 (Box 37, Folder 8)
- Boston, 1994-1995 (Box 37, Folder 9)
- Boston, 1996 (Box 37, Folder 10)
- Boston: Strategy Study, 1994 (Box 37, Folder 11)
- Boston: Implementation, 1994-1996 (Box 37, Folder 12)
- Boston: Project, 1994-1995 (Box 37, Folder 13)
- Boston: Engineering Project, 1994 (Box 37, Folder 14)
- Bridgton Knitting Mills [folder 1 of 2], 1997-1998 (Box 37, Folder 15)
- Bridgton Knitting Mills [folder 2 of 2], 1997-1998 (Box 37, Folder 16)
- Bridgton: Newsletter, 1997 (Box 37, Folder 17)
- Malden Mills: Lawrence Facility Opening, 1997 (Box 37, Folder 18)
- Malden Mills: Newsletter, 1997-1998 (Box 37, Folder 19)
- Malden Mills, 1996-1998 (Box 37, Folder 20)
- Malden Mills, 1996 (Box 37, Folder 21)
- Leslie Fay: Labor Management, 1994 (Box 37, Folder 22)
- Leslie Fay: Strike, 1994 (Box 37, Folder 23)
- Leslie Fay: Consulting, 1992-1994 (Box 37, Folder 24)
- Leslie Fay: Stakeholders, 1993-1994 (Box 37, Folder 25)
- Leslie Fay: Congressional Hearings, 1994 (Box 37, Folder 26)
- Leslie Fay: Letters, 1993-1994 (Box 37, Folder 27)
- Leslie Fay: Boycott, 1994 (Box 37, Folder 28)
- Leslie Fay: Articles, 1994 (Box 37, Folder 29)
- Leslie Fay: Clippings [folder 1 of 2], 1994 (Box 37, Folder 30)
- Leslie Fay: Clippings [folder 2 of 2], 1994 (Box 37, Folder 31)
- Leslie Fay: Time Magazine, 1994 (Box 37, Folder 32)
  June 13, pages 56-58
- New York Times Magazine, 1998 (Box 37, Folder 33)
  February 15, Fleece Article pages 20-23
- Amalgamated Clothing and Textile Workers Union (ACTWU): Conference, 1994 (Box 37, Folder 34)
- Amalgamated Clothing and Textile Workers Union (ACTWU): Labor-Management Committee, 1989-1990 (Box 37, Folder 35)
- Labor-Management Cooperation and Critique, 1995 (Box 37, Folder 36)
- Labor-Management Strategy, 1991-1994 (Box 37, Folder 37)
- Incubators: Fashion Institute of Technoloy (FIT), 1993-1994 (Box 37, Folder 38)
- Incubators: New York City, 1989-1990 (Box 37, Folder 39)
- Incubators: Elsewhere, 1987-1993 (Box 37, Folder 40)
- Justice, 1990-1994 (Box 37, Folder 41)
- ILG Network, 1993 (Box 37, Folder 42)
- Leslie Fay: Tour Reports, 1994 (Box 38, Folder 1)
- Leslie Fay: General, 1994-1995 (Box 38, Folder 2)
- Leslie Fay: Mediation Agreement, 1994-1995 (Box 38, Folder 3)
- Leslie Fay: Communications, 1994-1995 (Box 38, Folder 4)
- Leslie Fay: Conversation Process, 1995 (Box 38, Folder 5)
- Leslie Fay: American Committee, 1995 (Box 38, Folder 6)
- Leslie Fay: Facilitator Meeting, 1994-1995 (Box 38, Folder 7)
- Leslie Fay: Final Round, 1995 (Box 38, Folder 8)
- Leslie Fay: Deloitte Pre-report, 1994-1995 (Box 38, Folder 9)
- Leslie Fay: Interviews, 1994 (Box 38, Folder 10)
- Leslie Fay: Potential Consultant Background (Box 38, Folder 11)
- Leslie Fay: Justice (Box 38, Folder 12)
- Leslie Fay: Bad Faith, 1994-1995 (Box 38, Folder 13)
- Leslie Fay: Additional Scenarios, 1995 (Box 38, Folder 14)
- Leslie Fay: Newsletter, 1995 (Box 38, Folder 15)
- QWL/EI Process (Box 38, Folder 16)
- Industry Associations, 2000 (Box 39, Folder 1)
- Negotiation, 2000 (Box 39, Folder 2)
- Industry Associations, 1991-1995 (Box 39, Folder 3)
- UNITE: Miscellaneous, 1997 (Box 39, Folder 4)
- UNITE: Health and Welfare Fund Easter States, 1997 (Box 39, Folder 5)
- IGLWU: Miscellaneous, 1994 (Box 39, Folder 6)
- Binder, 1997 (Box 39, Folder 7)
- Outerwear Negotiations, 1994-1997 (Box 39, Folder 8)
- Contract Agreement, 1997 (Box 39, Folder 9)
- Association Lists, 1997-1998 (Box 39, Folder 10)
- Code of Conduct, 1997 (Box 39, Folder 11)
- Negotiations: Jay Mazur, 1997 (Box 39, Folder 12)
- Cost of Living Adjustments (COLA), 1991-2000 (Box 39, Folder 13)
- Reopener, 1997 (Box 39, Folder 14)
- Counter-Proposals, 1997 (Box 39, Folder 15)
- Contingent Workers, 1990-1997 (Box 39, Folder 16)
- Negotiation Update, 1997 (Box 39, Folder 17)
- Mobilization, 1997 (Box 39, Folder 18)
- Negotiations: Benefits, 1997 (Box 39, Folder 19)
- Distribution Center versus Drop-Ship, 1997 (Box 39, Folder 20)
- Distribution Center Issues, 1997 (Box 39, Folder 21)
- Consumer Price Index (CPI), 1987-1997 (Box 39, Folder 22)
- Negotiations: Union Presentations, 1997 (Box 39, Folder 23)
- New Warehouses, 1997 (Box 39, Folder 24)
- Breakaway Company Studies, 1997 (Box 39, Folder 25)
- Negotiations: Major Market, 1994 (Box 39, Folder 26)
- Negotiations: Code of Conduct Overseas, 1994 (Box 39, Folder 27)
- Negotiations: Labor-Management Issues, 1991-1993 (Box 39, Folder 28)
- Major Market Task Force on Benefits, 1994 (Box 39, Folder 29)
- Jay Mazur Notes, 1994 (Box 39, Folder 30)
- Negotiations: Regional Meetings, 1994 (Box 39, Folder 31)
- Negotiations: Staff Training, 1990-1991 (Box 39, Folder 32)
- Negotiations: GEB Sessions, 1994 (Box 39, Folder 33)
- Contract Language Task Force, 1993 (Box 39, Folder 34)
- Negotiations: Demands, 1991-1994 (Box 39, Folder 35)
- Negotiations: Warehouse Task Force, 1994 (Box 39, Folder 36)
- Negotiations: Media, Communications, Press Releases, 1994 (Box 39, Folder 37)
- Negotiations: Correspondence, 1994 (Box 39, Folder 38)
- Negotiations: Meeting Notes, 1994 (Box 39, Folder 39)
- Negotiations: Binder, 1991-1994 (Box 39, Folder 40)
- Amalgamated Clothing and Textiles Workers Union (ACTWU), 1991-1994 (Box 39, Folder 41)
- Negotiations: Strike Preparation, 1994 (Box 39, Folder 42)
- Negotiations: Mobilization, 1997 (Box 39, Folder 43)
- Negotiations: Liz Claiborne Task Force, 1997 (Box 39, Folder 44)
- Negotiations: Schedule, 1997 (Box 39, Folder 45)
- Funds, 1996 (Box 39, Folder 46)
- Negotiations: Meeting, 1997 (Box 39, Folder 47)
  March 14
- Negotiations: Warehouse, 1997 (Box 39, Folder 48)
- Negotiations: Communication, 1997 (Box 39, Folder 49)
- Negotiations, 1997 (Box 39, Folder 50)
- Contract Comparisons, 1991-1997 (Box 39, Folder 51)
- Warehouse Meeting, 1997 (Box 39, Folder 52)
- Negotiations: Carl Proper, 1994 (Box 39, Folder 53)
- GEB Outerwear Session, 1997 (Box 39, Folder 54)
- Negotiations: Language, 1997 (Box 39, Folder 55)
- Negotiation Memos, 1997 (Box 40, Folder 1)
- Major Market Negotiations Mailing Notes, 1994 (Box 40, Folder 2)
- Shops with Expiring Contracts, 1996 (Box 40, Folder 3)
- Association Codes, 1996 (Box 40, Folder 4)
- Alpha Firm List, 1996 (Box 40, Folder 5)
- Association Codes, 1997 (Box 40, Folder 6)
- Alpha Firm List [folder 1 of 2], 1997 (Box 40, Folder 7)
- Alpha Firm List [folder 2 of 2], 1997 (Box 40, Folder 8)
- Politics: Presidential Campaign, 1995 (Box 41, Folder 1)
- Campaign for New Priorities, 1992 (Box 41, Folder 2)
- US Congressman Gerry Nadler, 1995 (Box 41, Folder 3)
- Clinton Campaign: Industrial Policy, 1992 (Box 41, Folder 4)
- Clinton General Information, 1992-1995 (Box 41, Folder 5)
- Clinton General Information: Code of Conduct, 1995 (Box 41, Folder 6)
- Clinton Commerce Department: Ron Brown and Chicago Conference, 1993-1994 (Box 41, Folder 7)
- Clinton Commerce Department: Ron Brown and Prabhakar Package, 1993 (Box 41, Folder 8)
- Clinton Commerce Department: Corporate Governance (Box 41, Folder 9)
- Clinton Commerce Department: Briefing, 1994 (Box 41, Folder 10)
- Clinton Commerce Department: Briefing Follow-up, 1994 (Box 41, Folder 11)
- Clinton Commerce Department: National Institute of Standards and Technology (NIST), 1993-1994 (Box 41, Folder 12)
- Clinton Commerce Department: National Institute of Standards and Technology (NIST) Emspak [folder 1 of 2], 1992-1994 (Box 41, Folder 13)
- Clinton Commerce Department: National Institute of Standards and Technology (NIST) Emspak [folder 2 of 2], 1992-1994 (Box 41, Folder 14)
- Clinton Commerce Department: National Institute of Standards and Technology (NIST) Technology Reinvestment Project Grants (Box 41, Folder 15)
- Clinton Dunlop Commission, 1994 (Box 41, Folder 16)
- Clinton Dunlop Commission: IGLWU-DOL Communications, 1994 (Box 41, Folder 17)
- Clinton Dunlop Commission: Press Coverage and AFL-CIO Response, 1994 (Box 41, Folder 18)
- Clinton Dunlop Commission: Work and Technology Institute (WTI) Conference on International Evidence, 1993-1994 (Box 41, Folder 19)
- Clinton Health Policy, 1993 (Box 41, Folder 20)
- Clinton Health Policy: Health Care Briefing, 1993 (Box 41, Folder 21)
- Clinton Health Policy: ILGWU Proposal, 1992-1993 (Box 41, Folder 22)
- Clinton Health Policy: Ira Magaziner, 1992 (Box 41, Folder 23)
- Clinton Labor Department: Employment and Training, 1993-1994 (Box 41, Folder 24)
- Clinton Labor Department: High Performance Workplaces, 1993 (Box 41, Folder 25)
- Clinton Labor Department: New American Workplace, 1994 (Box 41, Folder 26)
- Clinton Labor Department: Retraining, 1992-1993 (Box 41, Folder 27)
- Clinton: US Budget, 1993 (Box 41, Folder 28)
  February 17
- Clinton Technology Policy, 1995 (Box 41, Folder 29)
- AFL-CIO Evolution of Committee Work, 1993-1994 (Box 41, Folder 30)
- AFL-CIO Work and Technology Institute (WTI), 1993 (Box 41, Folder 31)
- AFL-CIO Work and Technology Institute (WTI): Agile Project, 1994-1995 (Box 41, Folder 32)
- New York State Industrial Effectiveness Program, 1991-1994 (Box 41, Folder 33)
- New York State Legislature: Lobbying ILGWU Agenda, 1994 (Box 41, Folder 34)
- New York State Legislature: Sweatshop Legislation, 1994-1995 (Box 41, Folder 35)
- New York State: Pataki Administration Department of Economic Development, 1995 (Box 41, Folder 36)
- Port Authority (Box 41, Folder 37)
- Caret, 1995-1996 (Box 41, Folder 38)
- Case Study: Proper and Mathews, 1995 (Box 41, Folder 39)
- Work and Technology Institute (WTI): Brian Turner, 1997 (Box 41, Folder 40)
- Work and Technology Institute (WTI): Current, 1995-1997 (Box 41, Folder 41)
- Work and Technology Institute (WTI): Case Studies (Box 41, Folder 42)
- Mazur-Cuomo Meeting, 1993 (Box 41, Folder 43)
  August 19
- Mazur-Cuomo Meeting, 1994 (Box 41, Folder 44)
- New York City: Ruth Messinger, 1992-1994 (Box 41, Folder 45)
- New York City Planning Commission: Meeting with Jay Mazur, 1994 (Box 41, Folder 46)
- New York City Public Relations, 1992-1994 (Box 41, Folder 47)
- New York City Council: Living Wage Bill, 1995 (Box 41, Folder 48)
- New York City Council Hearing, 1993 (Box 41, Folder 49)
  June 24
- New York City Council Hearing on Job Creation, 1993 (Box 41, Folder 50)
- Ira Brophy, Brooklyn, 1990-1991 (Box 41, Folder 51)
- New York City Department of Employment, 1993 (Box 41, Folder 52)
- New York City: Barry Sullivan, 1991-1992 (Box 41, Folder 53)
- New York City Mayor Dinkins: Meeting Background Information, 1993 (Box 41, Folder 54)
  April 5
- New York City Mayor Dinkins: European Trip (Box 41, Folder 55)
- New York City Mayor Dinkins: Policy Statement, 1992 (Box 41, Folder 56)
- New York City Mayor Dinkins: Policy Statement, 1993 (Box 41, Folder 57)
- New York City Mayor Dinkins: Promotion and Development Proposal (Box 41, Folder 58)
- New York City Economic Development Corporation, 1987-1991 (Box 41, Folder 59)
- New York City Economic Development Corporation: Financial Aid, 1995 (Box 41, Folder 60)
- New York City Economy, 1995 (Box 41, Folder 61)
- New York City Entrepreneurial Government Report, 1993 (Box 41, Folder 62)
  May
- New York City: Mark Green, 1995 (Box 41, Folder 63)
- New York City Job Creation Report, 1993 (Box 41, Folder 64)
- New York City Partnership, 1993-1994 (Box 41, Folder 65)
- New York City Mayor Giuliani: ILG Background, 1991-1994 (Box 41, Folder 66)
- Address Books (Box 42, Folder 1)
- Day Books, 1979-1984 (Box 42, Folder 2)
- Day Books, 1985-1988 (Box 42, Folder 3)
- Day Books, 1991-1994 (Box 42, Folder 4)